غرامك شي عجيب و طبعك ما حصل
your love is wonderful thing, your "character" never happened
أحبك لو تغيب، و راضي بالأمل
I love you even if you're absent, and I am satisfied with hope
غرامك شي عجيب و طبعك ما حصل
your love is wonderful thing, your "character" never happened
أحبك لو تغيب، و راضي بالأمل
I love you even if you're absent, and I am satisfied with hope
حيران... و لا منك خبر
(I'm) Lost... And no news from you
سهران... وينك يا قمر
(I'm) Sleepless... Where are you, moon
و من شوقي آه
And from my longing Ouch
و من جرحي آه
And from my wound Ouch
أشكي و أقول: ويل ويلاه
I complain and say: wayl my wayl
من شوقي آه
from my longing Ouch
و من جرحي آه
And from my wound Ouch
أشكي و أقول: ويل ويلاه
I complain and say: wayl my wayl
آه قلبي معاك
Oh my heart is with you
لا ما نساك لا ما نساك
no it didn't forget you, no it didn't forget you
بأقسى الظروف
in the hardest of circumstances
نبضاتي أنت و عيوني، أنت اللي تشوف
my heartbeat and eyes is you, you're the one who sees
آه قلبي معاك
Oh my heart is with you
لا ما نساك لا ما نساك
no it didn't forget you, no it didn't forget you
بأقسى الظروف
in the hardest of circumstances
نبضاتي أنت و عيوني، أنت اللي تشوف
my heartbeat and eyes is you, you're the one who sees
خذني بهواك و أرحل معاك وين ما تروح
take me in your love and ill go with you wherever you go
و انت بعيد أبقى وحيد كلي جروح
when you're away, i stay alone full of wounds
خذني بهواك و أرحل معاك وين ما تروح
take me in your love and ill go with you wherever you
و انت بعيد أبقى وحيد كلي جروح
when you're away, i stay alone full of wounds
أسألك وين ذاك الحنين يا ناس وينه؟
I ask you where is that longing? people where is it?
قلب حزين مخلص أمين و الله يعينه
a sad heart, loyal and honest, and god help him
أسألك وين ذاك الحنين يا ناس وينه؟
I ask you where is that longing? people where is it?
قلب حزين مخلص أمين و الله يعينه
a sad heart, loyal and honest, and god help him
ما أدري شأقول علمني قول ضاع الكلاااااام
I don't know what to say tell me what to say words are lost!
عطني حلول و ابعث رسول و الا سلاااام
give me solutions, send a messenger, or a salam
ما أدري شأقول علمني قول ضاع الكلاااااام
I don't know what to say tell me what to say words are lost!
عطني حلول و ابعث رسول و الا سلاا-اا-اا-اام
give me solutions, send a messenger, or a salam
فرحني يوم.. بس لا تغيب
Make me happy for a day, but don't leave
و لو مهما كنت.. أغلى حبيب
And whatever you do, most precious lover
فرحني يوم.. و اجرحني يوم.. بس لا تغيب
Make me happy a day, wound me a day, but don't leave
و لو مهما كنت تبقى لي أنت أغلى حبيب
And whatever you do, most precious lover
و من شوقي آه
from my longing Ouch
و من جرحي آه
from my wound Ouch
أشكي و أقول.. ويل ويلاه
I complain and say: Wayl my wayl
و من شوقي آه
from my longing Ouch
و من جرحي آه
from my wound Ouch
أشكي و أقول.. ويل ويلاه
I complain and say: Wayl my wayl
من شوقي آه
from my longing Ouch
و من جرحي آه
from my wound Ouch
أشكي و أقول.. ويل ويلاه
I complain and say: Wayl my wayl
من شوقي آه
from my longing Ouch
و من جرحي آه
from my wound Ouch
أشكي و أقول.. ويل ويلاه
I complain and say: Wayl my wayl
ويل ويلاه
Wayl my wayl